Guide to the Alton Abraham Collection of Sun Ra 1822-2008
University of Chicago Library
- Series IX: Art and Artifacts
  - Interstellar Low Ways, album jacket, framed (Box 77)
  - Jazz in Silhouette, album jacket, framed (Box 78)
  - Jazz in Silhouette, album jacket, framed (Box 78)
  - Monorails and Satellites, album jacket, framed (Box 79)
  - Sound Sun Pleasure!!, album jacket, framed (Box 79)
  - Sun Ra, album jacket, framed (Box 80)
  - Sun Ra and his Solar Arkestra, album jacket, framed (Box 80)
  - Super-Sonic Jazz, album jacket, framed (Box 81)
  - Super-Sonic Jazz, album jacket, framed (Box 81)
  - A Tonal View of Times Tomorrow, album jacket, framed (Box 82)
  - We Travel the Space Ways, album jacket, framed (Box 82)
  - Claude Dangerfield, album cover artwork, framed (Box 83)
  - Claude Dangerfield, Music from Tomorrow's World, album cover artwork, framed (Box 84)
  - Evans, Jazz in Silhouette, artwork, framed (Box 85)
  - James Bryant, Sun Ra and his Arkestra, album cover artwork, matted (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - James Bryant, Sun Ra and his Arkestra, album cover artwork, matted (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - James Bryant, Sun Ra and his Arkestra, album cover artwork, matted (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - James Bryant, Sun Ra and his Arkestra, album cover artwork, matted (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - LeRoy Butler, Discipline 27-II, album cover artwork, matted (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Claude Dangerfield, Rocket Number Nine, album cover artwork, matted (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Claude Dangerfield, Super-Sonic Jazz, album cover artwork, matted (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Claude Dangerfield, Super-Sonic Jazz, album cover artwork, matted (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Claude Dangerfield, When Sun Comes Out, album cover artwork, matted (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Claude Dangerfield, When Sun Comes Out, album cover artwork, matted (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Claude Dangerfield, When Sun Comes Out, album cover artwork, matted (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Claude Dangerfield, album cover artwork, matted (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Claude Dangerfield, album cover artwork, matted (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Claude Dangerfield, album cover artwork, matted (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Claude Dangerfield, album cover artwork, matted (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Claude Dangerfield, album cover artwork, matted (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Sun Ra, Art Forms of Dimensions Tomorrow, album cover artwork, matted (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Sun Ra, Art Forms of Dimensions Tomorrow, album cover artwork, matted (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Angels and Demons at Play, album cover artwork, matted (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Angels and Demons at Play, album cover artwork, matted (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Cosmic Tones for Mental Therapy, album cover artwork, matted (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Other Planes of There, album cover artwork, matted (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Visits Planet Earth, album cover proof, matted (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - When Angels Speak of Love, album cover artwork, matted (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - When Sun Comes Out, album cover artwork, matted (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Unidentified album cover artwork, matted (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Aye, black-light painting, matted (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Black-light painting installation, photographs, matted (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Black-light painting installation, photographs, matted (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Black-light painting installation, photographs, matted (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Black-light painting installation, photographs, matted (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Saturn Research business card and logo artwork, matted (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Typographic designs, matted (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Tickets and handbill, matted (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - Broadside, matted (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - Sign, matted (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - Sun Ra, Art Forms of Dimensions Tomorrow, album cover artwork, matted (Box 90)
  - Jazz from Tomorrow's World, album cover artwork, matted (Box 90)
  - Saturn Records catalog cover artwork, matted (Box 90)
  - Black-light painting installation, photographs, matted (Box 90)
  - Angels and Demons at Play, album jackets (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Atlantis, album jackets (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Bad and Beautiful, album jackets (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Continuation, album jackets (Box 91, Folder 4-5)
  - Cosmic Tones for Mental Therapy, album jackets (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Discipline 27-II, album jackets (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Fate in a Pleasant Mood, album jacket (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - Interstellar Low Ways, album jackets, circa 1967 (Box 92, Folder 1-2)
  - Jazz in Silhouette, album jackets (Box 92, Folder 3-4)
  - The Magic City, album jackets (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Monorails and Satellites, album jackets (Box 92, Folder 6-8)
  - My Favorite Things, album jacket (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - The Night of the Purple Moon, album jackets (Box 92, Folder 10-11)
  - The Nubians of Plutonia, album jackets (Box 92, Folder 12-13)
  - Other Planes of There, album jackets (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - The Soul Vibrations of Man, album jackets (Box 93, Folder 2-3)
  - Sound Sun Pleasure!!, album jackets (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Sun Ra, album jackets (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Sun Ra and his Solar Arkestra, album jackets (Box 93, Folder 6-7)
  - A Tonal View of Times Tomorrow, album jackets (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - Universe in Blue, album jacket (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - We Travel the Space Ways, album jackets (Box 93, Folder 10-11)
  - Claude Dangerfield, color separations for album cover artwork, Interstellar Low Ways Sun Ra Visits Planet Earth/ Super-Sonic Jazz A Tonal View of Times Tomorrow (Box 94, Folder 1-4)
  - Angels and Demons at Play, album cover artwork (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Celestial Love, album cover label (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Collectors Items Volume I thru K, album cover artwork and proofs (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Discipline 27-II, album cover layout (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - The Immeasurable Equation, metal printing plate and negatives (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - Music of the Greater Space Age, album cover layout (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - Other Planes of There, album cover artwork (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - Other Planes of There, album cover layout (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - Space is the Place, production notes on blank album jacket (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - Visit Planet Earth, album cover layout (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - Lacy Gibson, I Wish I Had a Wishing Ring, fragment of album cover layout (Box 94, Folder 15)
  - Lena McLin, The McLin Ensemble Singing Spirituals, album cover artwork (Box 94, Folder 16)
  - Recording studio architectural drawings (Box 94, Folder 17)
  - Drawings (Box 94, Folder 18)
  - Photographs of artworks (Box 94, Folder 19)
  - Unidentified proof (Box 94, Folder 20)
  - Unidentified proofs and layout fragments (Box 94, Folder 21)
  - Fragments of album cover layouts (Box 94, Folder 22)
  - Audio Matrix, Inc., sample album jacket (Box 94, Folder 23)
  - Blank album jacket and type specimens (Box 94, Folder 24)
  - Empty album jacket mailed from Sun Ra to Alton Abraham (Box 94, Folder 25)
  - Lettering transfer sheets (Box 94, Folder 26)
  - Angels and Demons at Play, album cover proofs (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Art Forms of Dimensions Tomorrow, album cover proofs (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Atlantis, album cover proofs (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Collectors Items Volumes I Through IX, album cover proofs (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Continuation, album cover proofs (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Cosmic Tones for Mental Therapy, album cover proofs (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Discipline 27-II, album cover proofs (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Fate in a Pleasant Mood, album cover proofs (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Holiday for Soul Dance, album cover proofs (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Jazz in Silhouette, album cover proofs (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - Magic City, album cover proofs (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - My Brother the Wind, album cover proofs (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - Night of the Purple Moon, album cover proofs (Box 95, Folder 13)
  - Nubians of Plutonia, album cover proofs (Box 95, Folder 14)
  - Other Planes of There, album cover proofs (Box 95, Folder 15)
  - The Soul Vibrations of Man, album cover proofs (Box 95, Folder 16)
  - Sound Sun Pleasure, album cover proofs (Box 95, Folder 17)
  - Strange Strings, album cover proofs (Box 95, Folder 18)
  - Super-Sonic Jazz, album cover proofs (Box 95, Folder 19)
  - Universe in Blue, album cover proofs (Box 95A, Folder 20)
  - Visits Planet Earth, album cover proofs (Box 95A, Folder 21)
  - We Travel the Space Ways, album cover proofs (Box 95A, Folder 22)
  - When Sun Comes Out, album cover proofs (Box 95A, Folder 23)
  - Unidentified Sun Ra album cover proofs (Box 95A, Folder 24)
  - Lacy Gibson, Wishing Ring, album cover proofs (Box 95A, Folder 25)
  - Sketch pad with fragmentary design material and notes laid in (Box 95A, Folder 26)
  - When Sun Comes Out, album cover artwork (Box 95A, Folder 27)
  - Impulse Records advertisement layout (Box 95A, Folder 28)
  - V. Short, drawing (Box 95A, Folder 29)
  - Photograph of artwork (Box 95A, Folder 30)
  - Atlantis, album cover layout (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Atlantis, album cover proofs (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Album cover proofs, Bad and Beautiful Jazz in Silhouette Monorails and Satellites (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Nuits de la Fondation Maeght, album cover proof (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Album cover proofs, Pathways to Unknown Worlds Secrets of the Sun Universe in Blue (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Proofs of artworks (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Angels and Demons at Play, printing job file (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Atlantis, printing job file (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Fate in a Pleasant Mood, printing job file (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Magic City, printing job file (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Unidentified printing job files (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - "The Space Music of Sun Ra," brochure design (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Drawings (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Sun Ra, photocopied artworks (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Fragmentary design material (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - "LP's by Sun Ra and his Arkestra," signs (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Saturn Research business card and logo, proofs (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - "Hot Hits Fresh from the Sun," broadside layout (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - Saturn "II" Research letterhead, layout and samples (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - Atra Productions letterhead, layout and samples (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - Record label artwork (Box 98, Folder 10)
  - Record labels (Box 98, Folder 11)
  - Record label sheets (Box 98, Folder 12)
  - Record label sheets (Box 98, Folder 13)
  - Record label sheets (Box 98, Folder 14)
  - Record label sheets (Box 98, Folder 15)
  - The Soul Vibrations of Man, Side A, record labels (Box 99)
  - The Soul Vibrations of Man, Side B, record labels (Box 99)
  - Taking a Chance on Chances, Side A, record labels (Box 99)
  - Angels and Demons at Play, record labels (Box 100)
  - Art Forms of Dimensions Tomorrow, Side A, record labels (Box 100)
  - "Cosmo Drama," Side B, record labels (Box 100)
  - Interstellar Low Ways, Side B, record labels (Box 100)
  - "Love in Outerspace," Side A, record labels (Box 100)
  - "Mayan Temple," Side B, record labels (Box 100)
  - Nidhamu, Side A, record labels (Box 100)
  - Nidhamu, Side B, record labels (Box 100)
  - "Sub Underground Series," Side A, record labels (Box 100)
  - "Sub Underground Series," Side B, record labels (Box 100)
  - Taking a Chance on Chances, Side B, record labels (Box 100)
  - Magic City, Side A, record labels (Box 101)
  - Space is the Place, record labels (Box 101)
  - The Soul Vibrations of Man, Side D, record labels (Box 101)
  - "Message to Earthman," Side, record labels (Box 102)
  - Nidhamu, Side B, record labels (Box 102)
  - "The Perfect Man," Side B, record labels (Box 102)
  - "Space is the Place," Side A, record labels (Box 102)
  - "The Sun Man Speaks," Side A, record labels (Box 102)
  - We Travel the Space Ways, Side B, record labels (Box 102)
  - Bad and Beautiful, Side B, record labels (Box 103)
  - Cosmo Earth Fantasy, Side B, record labels (Box 103)
  - Deep Purple, Side B record labels (Box 103)
  - Nature's God, Side A, record labels (Box 103)
  - Nature's God, Side B, record labels (Box 103)
  - "Sub Underground Series," Side B, record labels (Box 103)
  - Bad and Beautiful, Side B, record labels (Box 104)
  - Cosmic Tones for Mental Therapy, Side B, record labels (Box 104)
  - "Cosmo Drama," Side B, record labels (Box 104)
  - Interstellar Low Ways, Side A, record labels (Box 104)
  - Interstellar Low Ways, Side B, record labels (Box 104)
  - Magic City, Side B, record labels (Box 104)
  - Monorails and Satellites, Side B, record labels (Box 104)
  - Sound Sun Pleasure, Side A, record labels (Box 104)
  - Some Blues But Not The Kind That's Blue, Side A, record labels (Box 104)
  - Some Blues But Not The Kind That's Blue, Side B, record labels (Box 104)
  - "Sub Underground Series," Side B, record labels (Box 104)
  - Atlantis, Side A, record labels (Box 105)
  - Bad and the Beautiful, Side A, record labels (Box 105)
  - Cosmo Earth Fantasy, Side A, record labels (Box 105)
  - Outerspaceways Inc., Side B, record labels (Box 105)
  - Pat Patrick and the Baritone Saxophone Retinue, Sound Advice, Side B, record labels (Box 105)
  - "Sub Underground Series," Side A, record labels (Box 105)
  - Art Forms of Dimensions Tomorrow, Side A, record labels (Box 106)
  - Horizon, Side A, record labels (Box 106)
  - Deep Purple, Side A record labels (Box 106)
  - Strange Strings, Side A, record labels (Box 106)
  - Strange Strings, Side B, record labels (Box 106)
  - "Sub Underground Series," Side A, record labels (Box 106)
  - Record labels (Box 107)
  - Record labels (Box 108)
  - Record labels (Box 109)
  - Art Forms of Dimensions Tomorrow, front cover, printing block (Box 110)
  - Other Planes of There, front cover, printing block (Box 110)
  - Cosmic Tones for Mental Therapy, front cover, two printing blocks (Box 111)
  - Art Forms of Dimensions Tomorrow, back title, printing block (Box 112)
  - Other Planes of There, "SRA" logo, printing block (Box 112)
  - Thoth Intergalactic logo, two printing blocks (Box 112)
  - Art Forms of Dimensions Tomorrow, inset abstraction, printing block (Box 113)
  - Saturn Records catalog cover, printing block (Box 113)
  - Saturn Records album list, printing block (Box 113)
  - Arkestra member list, printing block (Box 113)
  - Thoth Intergalactic logo, printing block (Box 113)
  - Cosmic Tones for Mental Therapy, inset image, printing block (Box 114)
  - Arkestra member list, printing block (Box 114)
  - Other Planes of There, registration, printing block (Box 114)
  - Saturn Records mailing address, two printing blocks (Box 114)
  - "The Shadow of the Fire," and "The Potential," printing block (Box 114)
  - Three pyramid ornaments (Box 115)
  - Three orb ornaments (Box 116)
  - "Alton E. Abraham" stamp (Box 117)
  - "Saturn Records" stamp (Box 117)
  - "Thoth Intergalactic Productions" stamp (Box 117)
  - "Saturn 'II' Research" stamp (Box 117)
  - "Promotional Use" stamp (Box 117)
  - "Air Mail" stamp (Box 117)
  - "Special Delivery" stamp (Box 117)
  - Saturn "II" Research, address and copyright statement, type pieces (Box 118)
  - Leather pouch containing astrological inscription (Box 118)
  - Wallet (Box 118)
  - Two kazoos (Box 118)
  - Tuning fork (Box 118)
  - Quartz crystal (Box 118)
  - Door keys (Box 118)
  - Insignia pin (Box 118)
  - 45 rpm record adapter (Box 118)
  - Metal ornament (Box 118)
  - Magnifying lens (Box 119)
  - Tarot cards (Box 119)
  - Sun Ra sticker labels (Box 119)
  - Album title sticker labels (Box 120)
  - Saturn Research sticker labels (Box 121)
  - Mbira (Box 122)
  - Necklace (Box 123)
  - Letter opener (Box 123)
  - Craft paper (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - Mars Marine bumper stickers (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - Printed ephemera, Shelby Hotel Rainbow Room, guest pass Roosevelt University sticker Syrian apricot paste label (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - Homemade musical instrument [Item on loan through April 2024. Please see staff for more information.] (Box 125)
  - Cymbal with numerological inscriptions (Box 126)
  - Microphones (Box 127)
  - Briefcase (Box 128)
  - Drumsticks (Box 128)
  - Planisphere instrument (Box 129)
  - Plexiglass triangle (Box 129)
  - Cymbal (Box 130)
  - Eight metal record stampers (Box 131)
- Series X: Oversize
  This series consists of oversize material transferred from series I, II, III, V, VI and VII. It is organized into subseries corresponding to the arrangement of these series.
  Subseries 1: Biographical, contains newspaper clippings, a scrapbook, a Buzzard comic book, and a poster for the Hyde Park Art Center's 2006 symposium "Sun Ra: The Astro Black and Other Solar Myths."
  Subseries 2: Performance, contains broadsides, posters and newspaper clippings documenting Sun Ra performances.
  Subseries 3: Recordings, contains broadsides and posters promoting Sun Ra's commercial recordings, as well as a binder that housed the Tilman Stahl discography.
  Subseries 4: Verse, Prose and Notes, contains oversize proof sheets of pages of the Immeasurable Equation.
  Subseries 5: Business Records, contains financial records, correspondence, publicity material, notes and blank legal forms.
  Subseries 6: Alton Abraham, contains publications, clippings, sheet music and ephemera. Included are several large-format posters and radical publications.
  - Subseries 1: Biographical
    - Scrapbook, 1962-1967 (Box 132)
    - Scrapbook page, 1968 (Box 132)
    - Tam Fiofori, "Sun Ra's Space Music," Changes, 1970 (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - Nathalie Petrowski, "Jazz de l'espace et des astronautes," Le Devoir, 1978 (Box 133, Folder 2)
    - Chicago Defender, 1981 (Box 133, Folder 3)
    - Daryl Jung, "Attempting the Impossible," Now, 1986 (Box 133, Folder 4)
    - Stephen Beaupre, "In Support of the Sun Ra Presidency," Buzzard, 1992 (Box 133, Folder 5)
    - Hyde Park Art Center, "Sun Ra: The Astro Black and Other Solar Myths," 2006 (Box 133, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 2: Performance
    - Crouse Hall, Syracuse University, Syracuse, New York, circa 1960s (Box 133, Folder 7)
    - Carnegie Hall, New York, 1966 (Box 133, Folder 8)
    - Mexico tour, 1973-1974 (Box 133, Folder 9)
    - Happy Medium, Chicago, 9-10 September 1978 (Box 133, Folder 10)
    - Massachusetts College of Art, Boston, 26-29 June 1980 (Box 133, Folder 11)
    - First Avenue, Minneapolis, 1987 (Box 133, Folder 12)
    - Chicago Jazz Festival, 1988 (Box 133, Folder 13)
    - Ridley's, Philadelphia, circa 1980s (Box 133, Folder 14)
    - Glassboro State College Black Art Festival, Glassboro, New Jersey, undated (Box 133, Folder 15)
    - Space is the Place, circa 1974 (Box 134, Folder 1)
    - Performances, Ann Arbor Blues and Jazz Festival, 8-10 September 1972 The East, Brooklyn, New York, undated Sweden, undated (Box 134, Folder 2)
    - Les Halles, Paris, 13 November 1970 (Box DRAWER 9, Folder 1)
  - Subseries 3: Recording
    - circa 1970s-2000s, Esperanto recordings, circa 1970s Reawakening, 1994 El Saturn Records Deluxe Reissue Series, Atavistic, circa 2000s (Box 134, Folder 3)
    - Discography binder, 1983 (Box 135)
  - Subseries 4: Verse, Prose and Notes
    - The Immeasurable Equation, circa 1971-1972 (Box 134, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 5: Business Records
    - Ledger sheets, 1956-1959 (Box 136, Folder 1)
    - General correspondence, 1965-1976 (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - Sunset Records, catalogs, 1966 (Box 136, Folder 3)
    - El Saturn Records catalog, circa 1960s (Box 136, Folder 4)
    - Press clipping montages, circa 1960s (Box 136, Folder 5)
    - Lacy Gibson, posters, circa 1960s (Box 136, Folder 6)
    - Ledger, 1969-1970 (Box 136, Folder 7)
    - "Sun Ra and his Arkestra," booking posters, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 136, Folder 8)
    - Provinssi-Rock festival, Finland, poster, 1979 (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - Saturn Records, promotional mailings, circa 1970s (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - Notes, undated (Box 137, Folder 3)
    - Recording agreement forms, undated (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - Ramsey Lewis Trio, album cover proof, undated (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - Peter Brotzmann Octet, poster, circa 2008 (Box 137, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 6: Alton Abraham
    - House of Knowledge, "M.H. Hammurabi's Almanac Calendar History," 1962-1963 (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - "The Complete Works of Professor Hilton Hotema, circa 1960s (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - Ethiopian Research Library, "Let there be Light," 1952 (Box 138, Folder 3)
    - Psychic Times, 1975 (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - Silva Mind Control kit, undated (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - Medical Electronics News, magazine, 1966 (Box 138, Folder 6)
    - Apollo space flights, commemorative album, 1969 (Box 138, Folder 7)
    - Cadillac brochure, 1975 (Box 138, Folder 8)
    - American Institute of Engineering and Technology, blank diploma, undated (Box 138, Folder 9)
    - Minister J.M. Miller, "Gospel Spreaders for God," poster, circa 1950s (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - "Doctine Chretienne," poster, undated (Box 139, Folder 2)
    - Yucatan Peninsula, map, undated (Box 139, Folder 3)
    - American Medical Association, "Who Expects V.D. at a Time Like This?" poster, circa 1970s (Box 139, Folder 4)
    - Guerilla newsletters, 1968 (Box 139, Folder 5)
    - Yipster Times, newsletter, 1974 (Box 140, Folder 1)
    - Sepia, magazine, 1974 (Box 140, Folder 2)
    - Clippings and Chicago travel guide, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 140, Folder 3)
    - Music filler paper, undated (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - Sheet music, circa 1910s-1950s (Box 140, Folder 5-6)
    - Guitar instruction material, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 140, Folder 7)
    - Blank music score pads (Box 141)
    - Newspapers and clippings, circa 1960s-1980s (Box 142)
- Series XI: Restricted
  This series consists of personal financial records, academic records, medical records, and identification and registration documents transferred from Series VII.
  - Personal financial records, circa 1940s-1990s (Box 143, Folder 1-6)
  - Personal financial records, circa 1940s-1990s (Box 144, Folder 1-10)
  - Personal financial records, circa 1950s-1990s (Box 145, Folder 1-11)
  - Personal financial records, circa 1940s-1990s (Box 146, Folder 1-5)
  - Academic records, circa 1963-1964 (Box 146, Folder 6-7)
  - Identification and registration, circa 1970s (Box 146, Folder 8)
  - Medical records, circa 1970s (Box 146, Folder 9)